Benjamin Boswick

Master of Landscape Architecture Candidate - M3 Student

A hard-working individual who effectively prioritizes tasks, operating in both independent and group settings. With intense dedication towards academics, a consistent work ethic is displayed. Keeping an open mind is necessary for creativity and retaining new information and experiences in the field.

Education

Email

ben.boswick@gmail.com

Present

^{2021/09 -} MLArch., University of Manitoba

2018/09 -2021/05

B. Env.D., University of Manitoba

Website

https://boswick.design

^{2016/09} University 1/Faculty of Science, University of Manitoba 2018/05

Hard Skills

Experience

Microsoft Office

Present

2021/05 -Sales Associate

McMunn and Yates Building Supplies (600 Pembina Highway)

Adobe InDesign

2017/05 -2019/11

Created and managed sales orders through a Point of Sales system

• Developed quotes for various products and structural packages

Adobe Photoshop

2015/02 -2016/10

Direct customer service

Tactful handling of challenging situations

• Attained knowledge of an array of products in every department

Assembled merchandising displays

Operated and maintained necessary machinery

Provided ancillary services outside and off-site

TwinMotion

AutoCAD

Rhino3D

SketchUp

Adobe Illustrator

VectorWorks

Soft Skills

Associations

2020-21 Student Mentor and Ambassador

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

· Providing advice and guidance to peers

• Participating as a faculty representative in various events

Communication

Collaboration

2020-21

Student Mentorship Program Cofounder

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

Coordinating student mentoring groups

• Ensuring success of participating mentors and mentees

Interpersonal Skills Time Management

2020-21

Graduation Committee Treasurer

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Student Architecture Society

Managing committee finances

Communicating and maintaining faculty wear inventory

Dedication

Estimation

2019-21 Student Affiliate

Manitoba Association of Landscape Architects (MALA)

Problem Solving

Merchandising

Publications

2019-20 "Urban Orchard", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 29 (Individual Project)

2018-19 "Untitled", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 28 (Collaborative Project)